ARJUN PUNEKAR

apunekar95@gmail.com | # 0424 073 944

KEY PROJECTS AND TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

Personal portfolio - https://arjunpunekar.netlify.app

Portfolio that showcases my main projects and highlights my experience below. It is built using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Useful Publishing - https://useful-publishing.netlify.app/

Real client project for a new small publisher. Design, functionality and assets have all been provided by the client. This is built using React. Currently there is no backend or user authentication, but I am in the process of building this using Express, Node JS and Mongo DB. User passwords will be hashed with Bcrypt and user authentication/authorisation will be handled using JWT.

To-Do List - https://arjunpunekar-todolist.netlify.app/

With this project, users are able to manage tasks in a sleek and intuitive interface. The React frontend ensures a responsive and dynamic user experience, allowing users to create, update, and delete tasks with ease. This is powered by Node and Express, with data stored in a Mongo DB cloud cluster.

EDUCATION

Coursera: Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate, 2023 (In progress 3/9 courses complete)

- Introduction to Front-End development
- Programming with JavaScript
- Version Control
- · HTML and CSS in depth
- React Basics
- Advanced React
- Principles of UX/UI design

Udemy: Web Developer Bootcamp by Colt Steele, 2022

- · HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Terminal
- Node
- Express RESTFUL routes
- Mongo DB schemas, validations, Mongoose

Diploma of Chartered Accounting CAANZ, 2019 - 2021

• Financial Reporting, Management Accounting, Audit & Assurance, Taxation Australia, Capstone

Bachelor of Commerce, UNSW 2015 – 2018

- Majors in Accounting and Finance
- UNSW Business Society
- University Games Medallist 2017-2018

High School Certificate, Sydney Boys High School 2008 – 2013

- SBHS First XI Football Captain 2013
- Combined GPS representative 2011, 2012, 2013
- Chess age captain 2008, 2009, 2010

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL INSIGHTS ANALYST, RETAIL INSIGHT, 2022 - Current

- Optimised alerting algorithm to recover an additional \$1.2m in lost sales for a retail client
- Implemented and tested an alert exclusion and suppression engine which increased alert accuracy by 12%
- · Implemented new store clustering methodology to improve lost sales recovery for retailers
- · Prepare and build weekly reports for retail clients to support commercial decision making
- Recent transition to Data Engineering projects, including updating and creating new ETLs
- Tools used include Python, SQL, Snowflake, GCP, Azure Data Studio, Power Bi, SSIS, PowerShell, BCP and Holistics

CUSTOMER STRATEGY ANALYST, WESFARMERS, 2021 – 2022

- Built an inventory relocation algorithm to identify and transfer inventory to deficit warehouses, decreasing lead times on several lines by 50%
- Built financial models to support commercial decision making
- Created and maintained robust suites of reporting on Power Bi that illustrate performance across multiple stakeholder groups
- Supported functional teams by providing analytics and insights to make more informed commercial decisions
- Presented an intermediate excel training course to 250 employees
- · Tools used include SQL, Python, VBA, Azure Data Studio

AUDITOR, MAZARS, 2019 - 2021

- Financial audits of small, medium, large and ASX listed companies
- Analytical reviews, substantive testing and controls testing
- Preparation and review of financial statements
- AFSL compliance review of forecasts and budgets
- Implementation of new accounting standards IFRS 9 and IFRS 16 preparation and review of credit loss models and lease models
- Macro creation to standardise audit templates
- Mentoring of junior staff

EXTRA-CURRICULAR AND VOLUNTEER WORK

- Baulkham Hills Premier League Football 2018, 2019, 2020, 2021, 2022, 2023
- Sydney Dogs and Cats Home 2017
- Kellyville Kolts Premier League Football 2017